McMurry, Don Papers 5655
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Don McMurry Papers
1865-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McMurry, Don
5655
10.5 cubic feet
10.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Consists of research material pertaining to the great Burlington railroad strike of 1888.
8230128
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5655 mf: Don McMurry Papers on Microfilm
Strikes and lockouts -- Railroads -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; McMurry, Donald Le Crone, 1890-
8230128
- Lexington Railroad Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Lexington Railroad Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Lexington Railroad Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lexington Railroad Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Lexington Railroad Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Donald L. McMurry Thesis Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Donald L. McMurry Thesis Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Donald L. McMurry Thesis Research, 1885-1897 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Research Index Files, 1890-1894 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Various Railroad Brotherhoods, 1890-1894
- Research Index Files, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  July 6, 1894-July 28,1894
- Research Index Files, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Various Railroad References
- Research Index Files, 1886-1893 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  1886-1893
- Research Index Files, 1885-1894 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Pullman, Cleveland, Railroad Strikes
- Research Index Files, 1885-1894 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Jefferson, Madison, War of 1812
- Research Index Files, 1885-1894 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Dept. of Columbia, Idaho, Colorado, Iowa, Kansas, Missouri, Oregon, Nevada
- Research Index Files, 1885-1894 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Pullman, Pinkerton
- Research Index Files, 1870-1898 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Research Index Files, 1870-1898 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Railroad Management, City govt, Strikes, Track Unions
- Research Index Files, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  June 26,1894-July 4 1894
- Research Index Files, 1889-1890 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Railroad Brotherhoods, 1889, 1890
- Research Index Files, 1887-1894 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  A-Z 1887-1894
- Research Index Files, 1888-1889 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Boycott, Strike 1888,1889
- Research Index Files, 1894-1896 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Injunctions, Pullman Strike, 1894, 1896
- Research Index Files, 1885-1886 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Board of Management
- Research Index Files, 1892 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Johnston, Pullman 1892
- Research Index Files, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Settlers, Problems 1900
- Research Index Files, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Strike, Arbitration
- Research Index Files, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Strike of '88, Results
- Research Folders, 1888-1894 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Research Folders, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Federation of the Railroad Brotherhoods McMurry, 1889-1894 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  1889-1894
- Federation of the Railroad Brotherhoods McMurry 2, 1889-1894 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Railroad Car Facts et. Al., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood Constitution and By-Laws, Railroad Research, 1952-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Research Folders, 1880-1894 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Research Folders, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Research Folders, 1877 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  References M-Z
- Research Folders, 1865-1893 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Act of 1888, Amendments, Newlands
- Research Folders, 1888 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  References A-K
- 2nd Round (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 2)
- R.R. Labor Investigation, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Burlington Strike, 1888 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Cochran (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Harper's Weekly - vol. XXXVIII-no.1960 + vol. XXXVIII-no.1961, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Lexington Group and related material (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Great Northern Strike (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Hogan's Army (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Federal Works Agency (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Articles Appearing in the Helena Herald, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Britte Miner (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Circuit Court-Misc. (Box 11, Folder 13)